

Skills

Languages

English Macedonian Albanian Turkish Serbian



Parts sales

Collaboration

Maintenance and Repair

Flexible and Adaptable

Excellent Communication

Computer Skills

SolidWorks 3D models

Employee management

Leadership

Hobbies:

- Playing Guitar
- ✓ Sport
- Reading

Contact

- Bitola, North Macedonia
- 078 298 470
- denissinanoski21@gmail.com

DENIS SINANOSKI

MECHANICAL ENGINEER. CUSTOMER CARE

Profile

Engineering student versed in reviewing plans, writing reports, researching solutions and implementing company procedures. Willingness to learn, follow instructions and work cooperatively within team environments. Computer competencies include various CAD programs and MS Office applications. Self-motivated, hard-working with broad foundation in engineering principles. Completes advanced academic projects demonstrating engineering support capability. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

Experience

Servicer

Komax | 2019 - 2022

- Attended project planning meetings to coordinate mechanical system designs, coordinate delivery timelines.
- Conferred with facility engineers to implement operating procedures, resolve system problems and provide technical information.
- Responded to customer requests efficiently and with knowledgeable assistance.
- Used coordination and planning skills to achieve results according to schedule.
- Calibrated, tested, and adjusted machine settings or controls in preparation for production operations.
- Manually set up machinery.
- Worked closely with engineers and assisted with testing of Komax products. And studied manufacturing processes used by Komax.
- Communicated with engineers to discuss methods to improve process and performance.
- Scanned documents and saved in database to keep records of essential organizational information.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.

Customer Care Representative

TaskForce | 2021 - Present

- Working with clients who have complaints, orders, requests from the company.
- Built strong relationships with customers through positive, friendly attitude fast response and able to handle angry customers.
- Strong Time Management.
- Responded to all customer inquiries thoroughly and professionally.
- Friendly attitude with the clients.

Education

Faculty of Technical Sciences

North Macedonia | 2020 - Present Mechanical Engineering